

# LARISSA M SII VA

Visual/Web Designer & Illustrator

I have experience as a freelancer graphic designer, in the production of advertisement pieces for companies and events. In the last few months, I sought to improve my knowledge in Web Design and to train myself in UI/UX Design. I'm an Architect and Urban Designer with work experience in residential, institutional and urban landscaping design projects.

+55 65 984085794	
/in/mslarissasilva	in
portfoliolarissa.netlify.app	Ė
mslarissasilva@gmail.com	$\sim$

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Designer & Artist**

Studio Larissa Machado

Full Time - Personal Office | 2021 - 2022

Freelance graphic design work and illustrations for tattoo work.

#### **Architect**

Larissa Machado Architecture

Freelance - Personal Office | 2017 - 2021

Architectural and urban designs, budget spreadsheets and documentation.

### **Urban Planning Coordinator**

Santa Rita do Trivelato Town Hall

Full Time - Office | 2021 - 2021

Urban planning, landscaping, architectural and urban revitalization projects, budget spreadsheets and documentation.

#### **Technical Advisor**

Santa Rita do Trivelato Town Hall

Full Time - Office | 2019 - 2020

Architectural and urban designs, budget spreadsheets and documentation with the Department of Engineering and Architecture.

#### **Arts Instructor & Graphic Designer**

Santa Rita do Trivelato Municipal Education and Culture Division

Full Time - Office | 2019 - 2019

Traditional arts instructor (painting and drawing) for children and teens. Graphic design work, such as logos, event posters and product designs.

#### **English as a Second Language Teacher**

**CCAA Language Centre** 

Full Time - Office | 2018 - 2018

Preparation and administration of classes in the English language, from basic to advanced levels.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Architecture and Urban Design (BA)

Universidade do Estado de Mato Grosso, Barra do Bugres, MT, Brazil.

2010-2016

#### **SKILLS**

Photoshop Figma UI/IX Design HTML & CSS Illustration Canva

#### **LANGUAGE**

English Portuguese Spanish Italian

#### **INTERESTS**

Reading

Film & TV



Programming



Photography



Travel



Gaming

#### **COURSES**

UI/UX (Coursera)

Figma for UI UX Design (Udemy) Revit 2021 Essential (Udemy) Brand Positioning and Marketing Communication (Udemy)

User Experience Fundamentals (Udemy)